{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was July 22, 2021, when the average temperature of the Earth's land and ocean surfaces was 1.04 degrees Celsius above the 20th century",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.9 °C (201.0 °F) at Furnace Creek, California, United States, on 15 July 19",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 129.2 degrees Fahrenheit (53.9 degrees Celsius) in Death Valley, California, on July 10, 1913.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.8 °F) on 10 August 2010, at 81.8°S 59.3°E",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.4 °F), measured in ʽAziziya, Libya on 13 September 1922, was reassessed in",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.5 °C (121.1 °F),Odienne,26 January 2025[36",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "12 July 2019, in Ouargla, Algeria.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "10 July 1913, Furnace Creek, California, USA.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.5 °F),\"Ejeda, Atsimo-Andrefana\",? [37]",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The highest temperature ever recorded on Earth was 56.7°C (134°F) in Death Valley, California, on July 10, 1913.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.6 °F),Jeddah,22 June 2010[74][28]",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024, by Christopher C. Burt, Weather Underground, 2014.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.9 °C (201.0 °F) at Furnace Creek, California, United States, on 15 July 1972.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024, by Christopher C. Burt, Weather Underground, 2014.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024. Burt, a weather historian writing for Weather Underground, believes that the 1913 Death Valley reading is \"a myth",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.4 °F), measured in ʽAziziya, Libya on 13 September 1922, was reassessed in",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.0 °F),\"Koundara, Boké Region\",29 March 2017[35]",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.2 °F),Sheung Shui,24 July 2022[50]",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.9 °C (121.8 °F),Farah,August 2009[46]",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 3
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "May 22, 1960",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.0",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "July 22, 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "July 22, 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "July 22, 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was July 22, 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "July 22, 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.3 Ms,",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "May 22, 1960, Valdivia, Chile, 9.4–9.6",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.6,\"Turkey, Kırşehir Province\",10.0,IX,224",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "May 22, 1960, Valdivia, Chile, 9.4–9.6",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "July 22, 2024.0 Mw,Death toll may have been a historical conflation with earthquakes on November 1137 in the Jazira plain and the 1138",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.0,XI,10000",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "July 22, 2024.0,X,\"12,000–15,000\"",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "May 22, 1960",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.0",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "July 22, 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "July 22, 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.3 Ms,",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was on July 22, 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record globally was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.0,IX,1001",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.6,\"Chile, Valparaíso Region\",10.0,IX,1000",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.0,\"China, Sichuan\",11.0,X,\"2,175–2,204\"",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "22 July 2024.0,IX,\"1,000–1,500\"",
      "needle": "The warmest day on record for the entire planet was 22 July 2024.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "When was the hottest day ever recorded globally?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ]
}